geantonline.ae 2017-09-07

# Privacy Policy

**The Main Point**  
Your privacy is extremely important to us. At Geant Online we won't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
  
If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please get in touch with Geant Online Customer Service by phoning **800 Gdirect(4347328)** or email us at [assist@geantonline.ae](mailto:assist@geantonline.ae)  
  
Geant Online’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while you are using our website.  
  
Our Privacy Policy is a part of our general Terms of Service. We have added it separately here so that it’s easy for you to find. **Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, Geant Online collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available. This includes such information as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and date and time of each visitor request. Geant Online’s purpose for collecting non-personally identifying information is to help us better understand how our visitors use the website. From time to time, Geant Online may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  
  
Geant Online also collects potentially personally-identifying information, for example Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users. Geant Online will only disclose logged in user IP addresses under the same circumstances that we use to disclose personally-identifying information. These circumstances are described in the paragraph Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information below. **Personally-Identifying Information  
**Certain visitors to Geant Online websites choose to interact with us in ways that require Geant Online to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that Geant Online gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. Visitors who sign up for an account are asked to provide a username and email address. Those who make purchases are asked to provide additional information including, when required, the personal and financial information we need to process the transactions. In each case Geant Online collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the website visitor’s interaction with Geant Online (e.g. to process and deliver the customer’s order).  
  
Geant Online does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below (see Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information). Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities, for example, making purchases. **Aggregated Statistics**  
Geant Online may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its website. For instance, Geant Online may monitor the most popular products on the website and may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Geant Online does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below in the paragraph Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information.  **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
Geant Online only discloses information that is personally-identifying or potentially personally-identifying to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organisations that;   
(i) need to know that information in order to process it on Geant Online’s behalf or to provide services available at the Geant Online website, and   
(ii) have agreed not to disclose it to others.  
  
Some of these employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of the United Arab Emirates. By using Geant Online’s website you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Geant Online will not rent or sell information that is potentially personally-identifying or personally-identifying to anyone.  
  
Aside from its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations as described above, Geant Online discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena or court order, or when Geant Online believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Geant Online, third parties or the public at large.  
  
If you are a registered user of the website and have supplied your email address, Geant Online may send you email to tell you about new features, ask for your feedback, or just keep you up-to-date with the latest developments at Geant Online and our products.  **Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer. The visitor’s browser then provides this information to the website each time the visitor returns.   
Geant Online uses cookies to help identify and track visitors, their usage of the Geant Online Website, and their website access preferences. Geant Online visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Geant Online Website. Customers who do this should understand that certain features of the Geant Online Website may not function properly without the aid of cookies. **Advertisements**  
Advertisements appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement so that they can compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. Geant Online’s Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Geant Online and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
